Narrator: 1
Speaker: I goes out and I fire up the old lawnmower
and about 25 minutes into cutting the grass I just happen to look up
and there stood two white gentlemen that I’d never seen before.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: I said, ‘Well, you got the wrong guy.
I ain’t done none of that.’
Narrator: 3
Speaker: I kept wondering, how a innocent man that was out cutting grass,
how do he go from cutting grass to all of a sudden his whole world is turned upside down,
and now the judge is saying, ‘I sentence you to death’.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: And they told me how proud they was that I was going home,
and even some gave me advice, and:
‘Pop, it’s a different world out there than what you was used to.’
Narrator: 5
Speaker: I don’t care when it raining,
I walks in the rain because for 30 years rain was not allowed to fall on my body,
and every time it rain I walks in the rain, it feel, like, so cool and so refreshing.